

# <Moisés Gonçalves\_>

## CONTACTS

https://www.linkedin.com/in/moises-goncalves-dev/



https://moisesgoncalves86.github.io/My-Portfolio/



http://github.com/moisesgoncalves86



+351 916 762 102



moisesgoncalves1986@gmail.com



Portugal

# **AWS reStart Graduate ABOUT ME!**

I have a unique story to share, with a varied career and wealth of experience. Starting in construction and then moving to hospitality before transitioning to IT.

I value hard work and dedication, and combining my practical skills with my interest in innovation and problemsolving has been a fulfilling experience. I am committed to learning and adapting to the rapid changes in the IT industry.

My diverse background gives me a unique perspective that I'm excited to bring to my next challenge.

Let's grow together!

# EDUCATION

## **Amazon Web Services (AWS)**

AWS re/Start Program Learner -Jun 2023 - Jul 2023

## <Academia de Código\_>

Junior FullStack Developer -Jan 2023 - Apr 2023

## Qualidade de Basto

High School Diploma -Nov 2002 - Dec 2005

## EXPERIENCE

#### **DEVELOPER**

Freelancer

2023-present

- A Rest API library catalog
- Technologies: Java, Spring Boot, Jira, Docker, Flyway, Gradle, Postman, GitHub

#### **WAITER**

**Pastry South Africa** 

2017 - 2020

... (Linkedin)

# CERTIFICATIONS

# <u> AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner</u> 👜



Amazon Web Services (AWS) Aug 2023

# AWS re/Start Graduate



aws Amazon Web Services (AWS) Aug 2023

# SKILLS

- Java
- Spring Boot
- Rest APIs
- MySQL
- JavaScript
- GitHub
- JUnit
- Mockito

- AWS Cloud
- Spring Framework
- Maven
- Jira Software
- Docker
- **Bootstrap**
- **CSS**
- HTML

# **PROJECTS**

#### **Backend**

- API for a library catalog (Spring Boot)
- API for deliveries (Spring Boot)
- RunPoorCadet (Java game)
- Map Editor (Java App)

### **Frontend**

- MyPortfolio (Js, HTML, CSS)
- Age Verifier (JS, HTML,CSS)

# LANGUAGES

- Portuguese
- English
- Spanish
- French

# HOBBIES

- Cycling
- F1
- Chess